# **Anton Zaharia**

London, CR0 7AF | +44 736 711 1009 | zahariaanton95@gmail.com Github | Blog | Portfolio | Linkedin

### **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

("There is no task shaped for Anton. Anton is task shaped!" CTO)

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript-based programming with a background in delivery services and restaurant management. Possess strong communication, decision-making, problem-solving skills and able to deliver great customer service, as well as excellent organizing and planning skills that enable adaptability, help to provide first-class service and meet deadlines.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### MASTERED:

Ruby, Ruby on Rails, SQL, Javascript, React, JQuery, Redux, JSX, ERB, HAML, Bootstrap, Bulma, CSS, SCSS, HTML, Google Cloud Functions, Cloudflare Workers, Web3

#### COMFORTABLE:

Python, AWS, Node.JS, React Native, Lua, Sinatra, Azure Cloud Functions, Webflow, Figma

Paypal, Stripe, Gooten, Zendesk, Slack, Facebook, Google, Twitter, GoDaddy, Cloudinary, Easy Project, Name.com, Syncfusion, (...)

# Artificial Intelligence:

TensorFlow, ML5.js

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Picfair** London, UK Apr 2021 - Present

Full Stack Software Engineer

- Led projects and successfully increased team productivity by 10% through process improvements.
- Successfully increased website speed by 30% through implementing front-end caching.
- Designed robust and scalable features for a high-traffic website with 99.99% uptime.
- Worked with the design team to create a new look for the website that was responsive and modern.
- Overhauled the obsolete legacy source code from production application, resulting in increased usability and decrease in crashes by 70%.

#### **Integrity Software Limited**

Full Stack Web Developer - Contractor

London, UK Jun 2020 - Apr 2021

- Successfully led 3 major projects, ensuring completion on time and under budget.
- Build and maintain applications for various clients, communicating with cross-functional teams regarding product and design.
- Transformed UIs using React, decreasing debugging time by 62% and increasing views by 31%.
- Developed, throughout the last 2-3 years, features and improvements for companies like: Nectain.com, proton-innovations.com, nash-fund.ru

London, UK Dec 2020 - Dec 2021

Ruby on Rails Developer - Part-time Volunteer

- Received coaching and support from peers and senior software engineers, and gained commercial experience using Ruby and Ruby on Rails.
- Designing robust, scalable and secure features and contributing in all phases of the development lifecycle.
- Partnered with interns, using code composition to redesign a clean API that offered flexibility to third parties.

## Full Stack Web developer - freelancer

London, UK Oct 2019 - Jun 2020

- Client-facing: Actively communicated with clients to understand project specifications and needs.
- Working independently to complete agile tasks which include writing clean, maintainable and efficient code.
- Utilized Agile methodology to manage website development projects from start to finish within the given timeframe and budget.

Hermes, Amazon, BCCP Multi-drop delivery driver London, UK Sept 2017 - Oct 2020

- Created a program, and planned every 2 minutes of the shift to set an estimated time of arrival.
  Resulted in 97.5 % completion of deliveries, collections, and ETA daily.
- Adhering to assigned routes and following time schedules resulted in 100% routes completion.

Vype

London, UK

Sept 2016 - Sept 2017

On-site surveyor - Contractor

- Traveling to circa 570 WHSmith UK stores, meeting all deadlines and performance requirements 100% completed.
- Communicating and working with 2-3 members of 5 different teams daily, resulting in a 5-star performance rating.

Papa Johns

London, UK

Store Manager

Sept 2014 - Sept 2016

- Respond to customer complaints and concerns in a professional manner to achieve 12% sales growth.
- Delivered excellent customer satisfaction achieving top-performing franchise in London.

#### **EDUCATION**

SuperHi

London, UK

London, UK

Crypto + Web 3 for Creatives course

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022

Flatiron School

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript and React program

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020

Udemy

Online, 2020

Certified Web Developer, Javascript Beginner to Pro Certificate

Zenva Academy

Online, 2018

JavaScript Programming - Learn by Creating a Cross-Platform Game Learn HTML and CSS by Creating a Responsive Company Website

Theoretic College 'Mircea Eliade'

Galati, Romania

Baccalaureate Diploma, Diploma in Social Science

2014

## **HOBBIES**

Parkour and Freerunning Video Editing Drones and Cameras

Youtube Video

Performed and Edited